Anthony Awuni, PMP

Product Management | Entry Level Front End - React | PMP | Esports (2) | Radio | Content Production

Accra Ghana | +233202090340 | awenjab2011@gmail.com

Summary

My colleagues would say I am a problem solver, with a wealth of experience in Customer Service, Product Development, and Digital Commerce. A certified PMP. I know the ins and outs of the tech, media, and telecommunications industries, and I'm super stoked to bring my skills and abilities to a top-notch organization.

If I had a superpower, forget controlling the elements like your typical superhero, I'd rock at persuasion! I have a knack for soothing grumpy customers and making things right. And hey, even without the power to shape-shift, I'm incredibly flexible and adaptable. I can handle any new task or responsibility with ease, thriving in a rapidly changing environment.

Skills

- Jira
- Freshdesk
- Intercom
- Django admin
- Team Leadership

- Project Management
- Scrum Processes and Agile Best Practices
- Product / Software Development
- Customer Support
- Dealing with irate customers

Experience

CUSTOMER SUCCESS COORDINATOR | 02/2023 - Current

Rising Academy Network - Accra

Remote

- Oversee entire customer support team.
- Ensured near-real-time response to all B2C customers on (Rising Academy Network's Math Tutor Software).
- Improved end-of-cycle satisfaction for product users.
- Maximizing customer outcomes and decrease our time-to-value for.
- Harnessing automation to Increase user engagement on.

SENIOR PRODUCT OPERATIONS ASSOCIATE | 02/2023 - Current

Mpharma - Accra, Ghana

Remote

- Project manager for Bloom integration (mPharma's proprietary retail and pharmacy transformation tool),
 implementation and adoption into new markets and facilities across regions.
- Developed documentation for process flow and onboarding of different business types into bloom across markets.
- Setting and reporting on SLAs to ensure process measurement, outcome, and overall improvement.

PRODUCT SUPPORT ASSOCIATE | 01/2022 - 02/2023

mPharma - Accra, Ghana

- Reduced the median first response time from 32 minutes and 11 seconds to under 5 minutes in the first quarter of 2022 and consistently maintained this mark.
- Achieved and maintained a CST score of 90% or higher through intercom while providing excellent user support.
- Leveraged on agile methodologies (Scrum, Sprints) to work on improvements, bug fixes, new features and
 enhancements of Bloom, mPharma's proprietary retail and pharmacy transformation software. This is based on user
 feedback and continues testing of the product.
- Working with Engineering, Product, Supply Chain, and other internal teams to troubleshoot and solve technical user problems
- Manage the global product support
- Troubleshoot user issues reported via Bloom help or other channels from across the market
- Follow standard procedures for proper escalation of unresolved issues to the appropriate internal teams
- Train users and set up new facilities on Bloom
- Drive the creation of our support documentation and processes to improve users' experiences and help scale our operations
- Provide on-site service to facilities within the country for training, support, or on-site troubleshooting as needed
- Continuously improve the global processes and ensure consistency in support across countries

REMOTE CUSTOMER SUPPORT AGENT | 09/2020 - 06/2021

5CA - Accra, Netherlands

• Email Support Tickets and Live Chats for Secretlab Gaming Chairs.

REMOTE DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST | 06/2019 - 07/2020

Wishpond Technologies - Vancouver, Canada

- Remote (WFH in Ghana) Online Campaign Design and Implementation, Leads
- Generation, Email Automation, ROI, Facebook and Google Ads, Website Tracking and Analytic, Proposal Writing
- Successfully handled 10 15 clients at a time.

COMMUNICATIONS ANALYST FOR TOBI CHATBOT | 01/2019 - 11/2019

Vodafone Ghana - Accra, Ghana

- Data Input for TOBi Chatbot.
- Training and Machine Learning for TOBi Chatbot using IMB Watson.
- Agile Methodology and Management using the scrum and sprint framework for product releases and improvement in TOBi ChatBot.

CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE ASSOCIATE | 04/2018 - 02/2019

Vodafone Ghana - Accra, Ghana

Successfully served customers by determining requirements; answering enquiries; resolving problems; fulfilling
requests; maintaining database, determining eligibility to create an outstanding customer experience while ensuring
the attainment of high Quality standards within the Contact Centre

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/tonyawuni/
- Portfolio https://anthonyawuni.netlify.app/
- Github https://github.com/BuilsaBoy

Education and Training

ULTIMATE PROJECT MANAGEMENT TRAINING For PMP - Case PM - UDEMY | 45hour Mandatory Course For The PMP Prep Exam

IPMC IT Training Institute - Accra, Ghana | Some College (No Degree)

Software Engineering, 11/2021

University For Development Studies - Ghana | Bachelor of Arts

Integrated Community Development, 12/2013

Certifications

• PMP, Project Management Institute.